Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/christianangelo-desamparado-35bb13244 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Support
Post-Sales Support
Interpret phishing simulation results

Certifications

CompTIA IT Fundamentals (ITF+)
Certification

CompTIA Cloud Essentials+ Certification

Mastercard - Cybersecurity Job Simulation

christian angelo desamparado

Student at ACLC College

Nasipit, Caraga, Philippines

Summary

After graduating two years ago, I delved into the family business, acquiring invaluable operational insights. Recently, a pivot towards Information Technology, especially cybersecurity, has been made. Actively engaging in penetration testing and mastering penetration testing tools, I also practice in helpdesk support roles, showcasing a passion for troubleshooting and problem-solving. This combined expertise positions prepares me uniquely at the intersection of business acumen and IT proficiency.

Experience

TryHackMe
CTF Player
October 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months)
https://tryhackme.com/p/christian.angelo

Municipal Disaster Risk Reduction Management Office IT Support April 2022 - July 2022 (4 months)

Nasipit, Caraga, Philippines

Education

ACLC College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2019 - 2022)